Guide to the Cornell Class of 1966 records, 1966.
Cornell Class of 1966 records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Class of 1966 records, 1966.
37-5-3621
Cornell University. Class of 1966.
1 cubic feet.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
1966 Class records and memorabilia, and white wool Cornell class sweater, with insignia.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
1966 Class records and memorabilia, and white wool Cornell class sweater, with insignia.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University -- Students.; Cornell University. Class of 1966.; Cornell University
Subjects:
Students
Form and Genre Terms:
Sweaters.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- 1966 white wool Cornell class sweater, with insignia., 1966 (Box 1)
- Class of 1966 25th reunion mailings 1, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Class of 1966 25th reunion mailings 2, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Class of 1966 30th reunion mailings, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Class of 1966 35th reunion mailings and varia, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Class of 1966 35th reunion affinity group, team 66 committee, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Class of 1966 40th reunion mailings, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Class of 1966 40th reunion housing, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Class of 1966 40th reunion catering, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Class of 1966 40th reunion campaign, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Class of 1966 40th reunion updates, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Class of 1966 40th reunion leadership dinner meetings, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Class of 1966 40th reunion contracts, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Class of 1966 45th reunion, 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Class of 1966 50th reunion, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Class of 1966 reunion bibles, 1996-2016 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Cornell 66 Silver bear club name tag, 1991; MU-2398A (Box 2)
- Cornell 66 Silver bear club name tag, 1991; MU-2398B (Box 2)
- Class of 1966 25th reunion pin, 1991; MU-2399 (Box 2)
- Class of 1966 40th reunion pin, 2006; MU-2400 (Box 2)
- Spirit of 31 Pass it forward pin, 2006; MU-2401 (Box 2)
- Cornell then, now, always pin an lanyard, 2006; MU-2402 (Box 2)
- Cornell bag, 2006; MU-2403 (Box 2)
- Slap watch, 2006; MU-2404 (Box 2)
- Podometer, 2006; MU-2405 (Box 2)
- Plates, 2006; MU-2406 (Box 2)
- Wrist lights, 2006; MU-2407 (Box 2)
- Bear paws pin light, 2006; MU-2408 (Box 2)